[
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"POR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"sevilla\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"sevilla\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"sevilla\".",
        "answer": "safi",
        "examples": [
            "carribean_trade",
            "english_channel",
            "kongo",
            "safi"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"TUR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"constantinople\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"constantinople\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"constantinople\".",
        "answer": "alexandria",
        "examples": [
            "aleppo",
            "alexandria",
            "crimea",
            "ragusa"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"ENG\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"english_channel\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"english_channel\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"english_channel\".",
        "answer": "lubeck",
        "examples": [
            "carribean_trade",
            "lubeck",
            "north_sea",
            "saxony"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"CAS\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"sevilla\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"sevilla\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"sevilla\".",
        "answer": "safi",
        "examples": [
            "kongo",
            "rheinland",
            "safi",
            "saxony"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"MOS\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"novgorod\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"novgorod\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"novgorod\".",
        "answer": "kazan",
        "examples": [
            "baltic_sea",
            "crimea",
            "kazan",
            "kiev"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"SWE\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"baltic_sea\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"baltic_sea\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"baltic_sea\".",
        "answer": "novgorod",
        "examples": [
            "cape_of_good_hope",
            "krakow",
            "lubeck",
            "novgorod"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"HAB\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"wien\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"wien\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"wien\".",
        "answer": "pest",
        "examples": [
            "genua",
            "pest",
            "ragusa",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"POL\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"krakow\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"krakow\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"krakow\".",
        "answer": "pest",
        "examples": [
            "baltic_sea",
            "nippon",
            "pest",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"VEN\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"venice\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"venice\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"venice\".",
        "answer": "ragusa",
        "examples": [
            "genua",
            "mexico",
            "pest",
            "ragusa"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"MNG\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"beijing\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"beijing\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"beijing\".",
        "answer": "hangzhou",
        "examples": [
            "girin",
            "hangzhou",
            "nippon",
            "yumen"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"DAN\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"lubeck\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"lubeck\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"lubeck\".",
        "answer": "saxony",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "laplata",
            "saxony",
            "sevilla"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"BRA\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"saxony\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"saxony\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"saxony\".",
        "answer": "wien",
        "examples": [
            "kongo",
            "lubeck",
            "rheinland",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"TIM\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"persia\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"persia\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"persia\".",
        "answer": "samarkand",
        "examples": [
            "doab",
            "ganges_delta",
            "hormuz",
            "samarkand"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"GEN\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"genua\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"genua\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"genua\".",
        "answer": "alexandria",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "cribea",
            "tunis",
            "valencia"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"BUR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"champagne\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"champagne\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"champagne\".",
        "answer": "bordeaux",
        "examples": [
            "bordeaux",
            "english_channel",
            "genua",
            "rheinland"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"LIT\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"kiev\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"kiev\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"kiev\".",
        "answer": "crimea",
        "examples": [
            "constantinople",
            "crimea",
            "krakow",
            "novgorod"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"MAM\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"alexandria\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"alexandria\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"alexandria\".",
        "answer": "aleppo",
        "examples": [
            "aleppo",
            "barsa",
            "ethiopia",
            "gulf_of_aden"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"VIJ\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"comorin_cape\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"comorin_cape\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"comorin_cape\".",
        "answer": "ganges_delta",
        "examples": [
            "doab",
            "ganges_delta",
            "gujarat",
            "gulf_of_aden"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"UBV\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"wien\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"wien\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"wien\".",
        "answer": "pest",
        "examples": [
            "pest",
            "tunis",
            "valencia",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"AYU\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"gulf_of_siam\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"gulf_of_siam\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"gulf_of_siam\".",
        "answer": "burma",
        "examples": [
            "burma",
            "canton",
            "ganges_delta",
            "malacca"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"KOR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"nippon\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"nippon\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"nippon\".",
        "answer": "girin",
        "examples": [
            "beijing",
            "california",
            "girin",
            "hanzhou"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"LXA\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"gulf_of_siam\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"gulf_of_siam\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"gulf_of_siam\".",
        "answer": "burma",
        "examples": [
            "burma",
            "canton",
            "chungdu",
            "malacca"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"JNP\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"doab\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"doab\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"doab\".",
        "answer": "ganges_delta",
        "examples": [
            "deccan",
            "ganges_delta",
            "lahore",
            "lhasa"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"AFG\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"lahore\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"lahore\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"lahore\".",
        "answer": "doab",
        "examples": [
            "doab",
            "gujarat",
            "hormuz",
            "persia"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"ADA\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"gulf_of_aden\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"gulf_of_aden\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"gulf_of_aden\".",
        "answer": "ethiopia",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "english_channel",
            "ethiopia",
            "hormuz"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"ZAN\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"zanzibar\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"zanzibar\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"zanzibar\".",
        "answer": "zambezi",
        "examples": [
            "canton",
            "cape_of_good_hope",
            "gulf_of_aden",
            "zambezi"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"PAL\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"rheinland\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"rheinland\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"rheinland\".",
        "answer": "gulf_of_siam",
        "examples": [
            "canton",
            "gulf_of_siam",
            "philippines",
            "the_moluccas"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"KAZ\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"kazan\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"kazan\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"kazan\".",
        "answer": "astrakhan",
        "examples": [
            "astrakhan",
            "novgorod",
            "siberia",
            "white_sea"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"HES\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"rheinland\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"rheinland\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"rheinland\".",
        "answer": "wien",
        "examples": [
            "champagne",
            "lubeck",
            "wien",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"WUR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"wien\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"wien\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"wien\".",
        "answer": "krakow",
        "examples": [
            "krakow",
            "pest",
            "saxony",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"BOH\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"saxony\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"saxony\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"saxony\".",
        "answer": "wien",
        "examples": [
            "krakow",
            "lubeck",
            "pest",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"NEV\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"champagne\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"champagne\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"champagne\".",
        "answer": "rheinland",
        "examples": [
            "bordeaux",
            "english_channel",
            "genua",
            "rheinland"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"NAP\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"genua\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"genua\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"genua\".",
        "answer": "alexandria",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "ragusa",
            "valencia",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"QAR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"persia\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"persia\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"persia\".",
        "answer": "barsa",
        "examples": [
            "barsa",
            "hormuz",
            "lahore",
            "samarkand"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"SHL\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"lubeck\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"lubeck\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"lubeck\".",
        "answer": "saxony",
        "examples": [
            "baltic_sea",
            "rheinland",
            "saxony",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"MAZ\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"krakow\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"krakow\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"krakow\".",
        "answer": "kiev",
        "examples": [
            "baltic_sea",
            "kiev",
            "pest",
            "saxony"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"RAG\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"ragusa\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"ragusa\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"ragusa\".",
        "answer": "constantinople",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "constantinople",
            "crimea",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"FLO\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"mississippi_river\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"mississippi_river\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"mississippi_river\".",
        "answer": "alexandria",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "ragusa",
            "tunis",
            "valencia"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"NOV\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"novgorod\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"novgorod\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"novgorod\".",
        "answer": "kiev",
        "examples": [
            "baltic_sea",
            "kazan",
            "kiev",
            "white_sea"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"GOT\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"baltic_sea\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"baltic_sea\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"baltic_sea\".",
        "answer": "novgorod",
        "examples": [
            "krakow",
            "lubeck",
            "novgorod",
            "pest"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"HSA\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"lubeck\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"lubeck\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"lubeck\".",
        "answer": "north_sea",
        "examples": [
            "baltic_sea",
            "north_sea",
            "rheinland",
            "saxony"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"HOL\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"english_channel\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"english_channel\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"english_channel\".",
        "answer": "north_sea",
        "examples": [
            "champagne",
            "lubeck",
            "north_sea",
            "rheinland"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"LOR\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"champagne\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"champagne\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"champagne\".",
        "answer": "rheinland",
        "examples": [
            "lubeck",
            "rheinland",
            "saxony",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"ULM\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"wien\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"wien\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"wien\".",
        "answer": "pest",
        "examples": [
            "krakow",
            "pest",
            "saxony",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"BOS\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"ragusa\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"ragusa\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"ragusa\".",
        "answer": "constantinople",
        "examples": [
            "constantinople",
            "crimea",
            "pest",
            "wien"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 45
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"BYZ\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"constantinople\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"constantinople\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"constantinople\".",
        "answer": "alexandria",
        "examples": [
            "aleppo",
            "alexandria",
            "crimea",
            "ragusa"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"OUC\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"nippon\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"nippon\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"nippon\".",
        "answer": "girin",
        "examples": [
            "canton",
            "girin",
            "hangzhou",
            "xian"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"PAP\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"genua\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"genua\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"genua\".",
        "answer": "alexandria",
        "examples": [
            "alexandria",
            "ragusa",
            "tunis",
            "valencia"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"SOO\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"nippon\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"nippon\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"nippon\".",
        "answer": "girin",
        "examples": [
            "beijing",
            "girin",
            "malacca",
            "xian"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "\nMoney flows from an upstream node directly to a connected downstream node. The amount of money flowing is determined by trading_power and the node's local_value. This flow is proportional to the moving country's trading power divided by the node's overall trading power. It's also proportional to the node's local_value, with no relationship to its current value. The flow of money benefits the downstream node and is detrimental to the upstream node. If, and only if, there are more than two downstream nodes connected to an upstream node, only the country hosting the merchant can decide the ratio of money flow.\n    \n================\n<Question>\n\nAssume that you are the ruler of the country named \"THU\". You and your competitions are on the system of trade in 1444.\nYou have one merchant to work on trade system. Our home node is \"saxony\". where should I allocate my merchant to steer trade to \"saxony\"?\n",
        "year": 1445,
        "goal": "Note that my goal is maximizing my profit on \"saxony\".",
        "answer": "krakow",
        "examples": [
            "english_channel",
            "krakow",
            "pest",
            "venice"
        ],
        "target_rdb": "eu4_1445",
        "target_gdb": "eu4",
        "question_num": 50
    }
]